It's true that the street you searched left no trace of the killer.
صحيح أن الشارع الذي فتشته لم يترك أي أثر للقاتل.
That's because he had been hiding elsewhere.
هذا لأنه كان مختبئًا في مكان آخر.
Right across the street, in an abandoned room,
على الجانب الآخر من الشارع ، في غرفة مهجورة ،
I found a footprint. Seven to eight inches long.
لقد وجدت بصمة.  من سبع إلى ثماني بوصات.
There was a dagger mark on the window.
كانت هناك علامة خنجر على النافذة.
It was probably to watch the scene of the murder.
ربما كان لمشاهدة مشهد القتل.
The killer must have waited here for a long time.
لابد أن القاتل انتظر هنا لفترة طويلة.
=Mysterious Tales of Chang'an=
= حكايات تشانغآن الغامضة =
=Episode 9=
= الحلقة 9 =
Footprint seven to eight inches long.
البصمة من سبع إلى ثماني بوصات.
Based on the mark and height of the dagger,
بناءً على علامة الخنجر وارتفاعه ،
he is estimated to be about seven feet tall.
يقدر طوله بحوالي سبعة أقدام.
The footprint was shallow.
كانت البصمة ضحلة.
So he must be thin.
لذلك يجب أن يكون نحيفًا.
By the direction of the mark, he is a left-handed man.
باتجاه العلامة هو رجل أعسر.
Master, you are amazing.
يا معلمة ، أنت مدهش.
I am just as well versed in the scene trace analysis.
أنا على دراية جيدة بتحليل أثر المشهد.
So now it is certain that the farmer in the back is not the murderer.
لذلك من المؤكد الآن أن المزارع الموجود في الخلف ليس هو القاتل.
This is a serial murder case.
هذه قضية قتل متسلسلة.
Yes.
نعم.
Besides,
بجانب،
I think...
أظن...
(Yongshun Pharmacy) Uncle, I can deliver this medicine.
(صيدلية يونغشون) عمي ، يمكنني توصيل هذا الدواء.
Take a break.
(صيدلية يونغشون) خذ قسطا من الراحة.
(Yongshun Pharmacy) Take care then.
(صيدلية يونغشون) اعتني بنفسك.
The time between killings is decreasing.
(صيدلية يونغشون) الوقت بين عمليات القتل آخذ في التناقص.
This means
هذا يعنى
his need for the thrill of committing a crime is intensifying.
تتزايد حاجته إلى إثارة ارتكاب جريمة.
Chief Shen, it's thanks to you
الرئيس شين ، شكرًا لك
that this street is so safe and secure.
أن هذا الشارع آمن ومأمون للغاية.
You're really good at flattering me.
أنت جيد حقًا في إرضاءي.
Chief Shen.
رئيس شين.
Come on.
تعال.
Coming.
آت.
You are a persistent and earnest lady.
أنت سيدة مثابرة وجادة.
I hope
آمل
you don't end up like your father.
لا ينتهي بك الأمر مثل والدك.
What's the matter, master?
ما الأمر يا سيد؟
Nothing.
لا شيئ.
Li Xinghe.
لي شينغ.
There you are.
ها أنت ذا.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Were they attacked?
هل تعرضوا للهجوم؟
What about Yao Zhan?
ماذا عن ياو زان؟
Hey.
يا.
Get up and drink your medicine.
انهض واشرب دوائك.
Yao Zhan, run!
ياو زان ، اركض!
It's okay.
حسنا.
I'm your father. I'm here.
أنا والدك.  أنا هنا.
Why do you have so many wrinkles
لماذا لديك الكثير من التجاعيد
at such a young age?
في هذه السن المبكرة؟
Master.
يتقن.
I'm here to deliver his medicine
أنا هنا لتوصيل أدويته
and take his pulse.
وقياس نبضه.
Do you also how to take a pulse?
هل يمكنك أيضًا قياس النبض؟
I can learn.
يمكنني التعلم.
Is he still unconscious?
هل ما زال فاقدًا للوعي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Did you find Yao Zhan?
هل وجدت ياو زان؟
I looked for him, but no luck.
لقد بحثت عنه ولكن لم يحالفني الحظ.
I guess
اعتقد
we'll just have to wait until he wakes up
علينا فقط أن ننتظر حتى يستيقظ
and ask him what's going on.
واسأله عما يحدث.
Okay.
تمام.
So
وبالتالي
if there's nothing else, I'll go back to Court of Judicial Review.
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر ، فسأعود إلى محكمة المراجعة القضائية.
Goodbye, master.
وداعا يا سيد.
Shen Mei!
شين مي!
Is Shen Mei home?
هل شين مي في المنزل؟
Official Chu.
تشو الرسمية.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Shen Mei's uncle said that she never returned to the pharmacy
قال عم شين مي إنها لم تعد أبدًا إلى الصيدلية
after she left to deliver the medicine in the afternoon.
بعد أن غادرت لتوصيل الدواء بعد الظهر.
Her uncle went out to find her,
خرج عمها ليجدها ،
but still couldn't find her either.
ولكن ما زلت لم تجدها أيضًا.
Did she not come home?
ألم تعد للمنزل؟
No.
لا.
I haven't seen Shen Mei back.
لم أر شين مي مرة أخرى.
Yes, Mei hasn't been home all day.
نعم ، لم تكن مي في المنزل طوال اليوم.
Where could she go at this time of night?
أين يمكن أن تذهب في هذا الوقت من الليل؟
Let's go out and find.
دعنا نخرج ونجد.
Shen Mei!
شين مي!
Mei is not taken by the bad guys, is she?
لا يتم أخذ مي من قبل الأشرار ، أليس كذلك؟
Stop talking nonsense and go find her.
توقف عن الحديث عن الهراء واذهب وابحث عنها.
Shen Mei!
شين مي!
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Official Chu.
تشو الرسمية.
Did you find her?
هل وجدتها
I've searched over there, but no findings.
لقد بحثت هناك ، لكن لم يتم العثور على نتائج.
Keep looking.
استمر في البحث.
Yes.
نعم.
No way.
مستحيل.
It can't be her.
لا يمكن أن تكون هي.
Shen Mei!
شين مي!
You know what?
أتعلم؟
When you were giving me the medicine,
عندما كنت تعطيني الدواء ،
your warmth, your eyes and even your touch
دفئك وعينيك وحتى لمستك
were just like my mother's.
كانت مثل أمي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It will be over soon.
وسوف يكون قريبا أكثر.
All right.
حسنا.
It won't take long.
لن يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلاً.
You make the call.
أنت تجري المكالمة.
Tomorrow.
غداً.
We'll do it another day.
سنفعل ذلك في يوم آخر.
You decide.
انت صاحب القرار.
It's the medicine that Mei delivered.
إنه الدواء الذي قدمته مي.
It's the medicine that Mei delivered. Look.
إنه الدواء الذي قدمته مي.  ينظر.
Yes.
نعم.
There is blood on the stone.
هناك دم على الحجر.
Master, hit me from behind with your left hand.
سيدي ، اضربني من الخلف بيدك اليسرى.
If the killer is left-handed,
إذا كان القاتل أعسر ،
then he must have a fresh wound on the back of his left hand.
ثم يجب أن يكون لديه جرح جديد في ظهر يده اليسرى.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
It seems that Shen Mei
يبدو أن شين مي
was indeed attacked.
تم الهجوم عليه بالفعل.
Keep looking.
استمر في البحث.
Don't give up even if there is only
لا تستسلم حتى لو كان هناك فقط
a glimmer of hope.
بصيص من الأمل.